Guide to the Archives Organization File Additional records, Section 2: Boxes 23-44
Archives Organization File Additional records, Section 2: Boxes 23-44
- Box 44, Folder (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 48: What Difference Does it Make?, Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 49: How Do GM Wages Stack Up?, Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
- Box 44, Folder (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Organization chart, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: GM Topics, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Looking Forward, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: comprehensive Hospital Care Certificate, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Autoqineer, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: Imagination, Money and Satisfaction, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: Agreement Between General Motors Corporation and the International Union of Electrical, Radio & Machine Workers, AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 8: Agreement Between General Motor Corporation and the UAW-AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 9: How to Obtain General Motors Educational Aid, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 10: Your Future With Buick, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 11: Your comprehensive Medical Expense Insurance Program, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 12: Your Job at Ternstedt, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 13: A BNA Washington Special report, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 14: Agreement Between General Motors Corporation and the UAW-AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 15: Remember that First Day?, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 16: Harrison Chronicle, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 17: Your GM Savings - Stock Purchase Program, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 18: Your GM Savings- Stock Purchase Program, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 19: Your Introduction to General Motors, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 20: Buick's on the Move, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 21: GM Personnel News, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 22: Standard Apprentice Plan, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 23: The GM Information Rack Service in Brief, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 24: Poster Previews, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 25: Various Sample Forms Used in Employee Rating, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 26: GMC News April, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 27: DR Clan, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 28: The AC Program for Selection and Training of Supervisory Candidates, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 29: Leave of Absence Military Service, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 30: General Motors Corporation Recreation, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 31: Tuition Refund Plan for Salary Employees, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 32: Supplement for Supervision, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 33: GEIC-MIC Questionnaire for All Employes, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 34: The "Right" Place to Retire, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 35: Your Benefits After Retirement, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 36: Comprehensive Group Hospital Care, M-75 Group Medical-Surgical Care, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 37: More Power to You, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 38: Only 5 Minutes, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 39: Look At General Motors, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 40: When Does 90 Days Equal 30 Years?, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 41: Working with General Motors, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 42: Opening the Door to Opportunity, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 43: Information for all Supervisors, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 44: Your Benefits After Retirement, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 45: Can I Get the Job?, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 46: Working Together at fabricast, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 47: A BNA Special Report, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)